culturazzi.org 2015-05-11

# Privacy Policy | culturazzi.org

**Email Addresses:**

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our website. We agree that we will never share your email with any third party, and that we will remove your email at your request. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form.  
 **  
** **Ownership of Information:**

Culturazzi is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites. Prior permission from the website must be granted before using any text, video, or image from Culturazzi for personal or commercial purposes.

**Comments/Blog:**

The website contains comment sections and a blog. We actively monitor and moderate these comments and the information on them is for constructive discussion purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. Culturazzi does not adhere to or validate the comments and opinions shared by the users. We encourage users to drop in comments that relate to the post and We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

**Cookies:**

Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish. Your browser has options to accept, reject or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent. Many of our advertisers use cookies in order to determine the number of times you have seen an advertisement. This is done to limit the number times you are shown the same advertisement. Culturazzi does not have access to this data.

**Traffic Reports:**

Our traffic reporting devices trace IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

**Your Privacy is important to us**

We will not rent, sell, distribute, lease or share your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect, incomplete or unlawful, please contact us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

**Legal proceedings:**

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but Culturazzi may need to disclose information when required by law.

**Links:**

Culturazzi sometimes links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Culturazzi.

**Contact Information:**

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
